# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the bin/rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)
question_a = Question.create(category: 'Business', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Which company is responsible for the animal toy fad introduced in 1993 as Beanie Babies?', correct_answer: 'Ty', incorrect_answer_a: 'Billund', incorrect_answer_b: 'Bandai', incorrect_answer_c: 'Wizkids')
question_b = Question.create(category: 'Religion', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Which of the Apostles of Jesus Christ had been employed as a tax collector in Galilee?', correct_answer: 'Matthew', incorrect_answer_a: 'Peter', incorrect_answer_b: 'Luke', incorrect_answer_c: 'Judas')
question_c = Question.create(category: 'TV', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Who sang the western theme song for the TV series Rawhide and the film Blazing Saddles?', correct_answer: 'Frankie Laine', incorrect_answer_a: 'Tex Ritter', incorrect_answer_b: 'Roy Rogers', incorrect_answer_c: 'Gene Autry')
question_d = Question.create(category: 'Geography', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'The Gila Cliff Dwellings National Monument is located near the mouth of the Gila River in which U.S. state?', correct_answer: 'New Mexico', incorrect_answer_a: 'Colorado', incorrect_answer_b: 'Arizona', incorrect_answer_c: 'California')
question_e = Question.create(category: 'Theatre', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Who attempted to revolutionize theater with the creation of his Theatre of Cruelty in his 1938 book The Theatre and Its Double?', correct_answer: 'Antonin Artaud', incorrect_answer_a: 'Lee Strasberg', incorrect_answer_b: 'Eugene Ionesco', incorrect_answer_c: 'Marc Blitstein')
question_f = Question.create(category: 'Music', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Which singer appeared as a regular on the 1970s sitcom Good Times and later as a teenager on the dance-oriented series Fame?', correct_answer: 'Janet Jackson', incorrect_answer_a: 'Paula Abdul', incorrect_answer_b: 'Alanis Morissette', incorrect_answer_c: 'Puff Daddy')
question_g = Question.create(category: 'Movies', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Which British actress exhibited herself sleeping in a glass case for a week at the Serpentine Gallery in England?', correct_answer:'Tilda Swinton', incorrect_answer_a: 'Glenda Jackson', incorrect_answer_b: 'Helena Bonham Carter', incorrect_answer_c: 'Emily Watson')
question_h = Question.create(category: 'Sports', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Which tennis player made a career comeback in 2001, winning her first Grand Slam singles titles, the Australian Open and the French Open?', correct_answer:'Jennifer Capriati', incorrect_answer_a: 'Tracy Austin', incorrect_answer_b: 'Kim Clijsters', incorrect_answer_c: 'Hana Mandlikova')
question_i = Question.create(category: 'Movies', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: "In the 1930s, which actor's film roles included Nero, Henry VIII, Captain Bligh, and Quasimodo?", correct_answer: 'Charles Laughton', incorrect_answer_a: 'Paul Muni', incorrect_answer_b: 'Leslie Howard', incorrect_answer_c: 'Paul Henreid')
question_j = Question.create(category: 'History', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Which country had "Papa Doc" Duvalier as its president from 1957 to 1971, and "Baby Doc" Duvalier as president from 1971 to 1986?', correct_answer: 'Haiti', incorrect_answer_a: 'Argentina', incorrect_answer_b: 'Brazil', incorrect_answer_c: 'Chile')
quesion_k = Question.create(category: 'Sports', style: 'multiple', difficulty: 'hard', question: 'Which NASCAR driver became the youngest winner of the Daytona 500 in 1997 at age 25?', correct_answer: 'Jeff Gordon', incorrect_answer_a: 'Jimmie Johnson', incorrect_answer_b: 'Matt Kenseth', incorrect_answer_c: 'Dale Earnhardt Jr.')
